(Leonard:)A little.
(Leslie:)There are so many things to talk about
before reproduction.
(Leonard:)I sure hope so.
(Leslie:)Besides shortness, what genetic
weaknesses run in your family?
(Sheldon(entering):)I'm sorry to interrupt.
Battery's dying. Continue.
(Leslie:)Uh, genetic weaknesses, right.
Um, there's the lactose intolerance.
Don't forget the male-pattern baldness.
(Sheldon(preparing an extension cord):)When his uncles sit around the dinner
table, they look like a half-carton of eggs.
Okay, yeah, my uncles are bald...
(Leonard:)...but my Aunt Edna is one of the hairiest
women you'll ever meet, so, you know...
(Leonard:)Sweet lady.
It always tickles when she hugs me.